thenisai.com 2003-12-04

# ::Thenisai - Privacy policy - Tamil songs/music portal - Tamil FM radio

**Thenisai.com's Privacy Policy**  
Personal information collected on our site will be utilized only for internal purposes to enhance user experience. We may also use email addresses or other personal information to contact users who directly communicate with us. For example, to notify users with the information they requested. We don't share any personal information provided by users with third parties, unless specified at time of collection. All information that is submitted on our site is stored securely and not shared with third parties. We take necessary and precautionary measures to secure our database. We request that all users to the Web site that are under the age of 18 not disclose or provide any personal information on this Web site unless they provide written authorization to us from their parent or legal guardian. We use cookies to deliver ads as per the frequency of visitors. We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time so users are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. 

**Advertisers**  
We work with various third party advertising networks like Commission Junction, Popuptraffic, . These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information. To find out more about how the ad network manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to [Commision Junction](http://www.cj.com/), [Popup traffic](http://www.popuptraffic.com/wsignup.php?tamilfm), [Absolute agency](http://click.absoluteagency.com/), [Click thru traffic](http://clickthrutraffic.com/scripts/signup.php?referer=tamilfm), [Search Traffic](http://www.searchtraffic.com/wsignup.php3?tamilfm), [Popup sponsor](http://www.popupsponsor.com/tracker/ref.phtml?ref_id=8316&s=0), [Focusin](http://www.focusin.com/). 

Please contact us (webmaster@thenisai.com) if you have any further questions about our privacy policy.
